(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
#hololivefesEXPO25_DAY1
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援 OK です
Attention: For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Vocal cheering is OK.
バンダイ、バンダイスピリッツより、
From Bandai and Bandai Spirits,
hololive EXPO 25の会場にある
at the hololive EXPO 25 venue,
特設ブースで、
at our special booth,
展示中の新商品をご紹介！
we're introducing the new products on display!
ホロライブ #hololive IF -Relax time- 天音かなた
hololive #hololive IF -Relax time- Amane Kanata
ホロライブ #hololive petit ラウンドクッション 天音かなた
hololive #hololive petit Round Cushion Amane Kanata
ホロライブエキスポ2025限定の、一番くじ特設フォトブースも展開中。
An Ichiban Kuji special photo booth limited to hololive EXPO 2025 is also now open.
モニターをタッチしてくじ券をめくり、出てきたデザインと一緒に撮影できます。
You can touch the monitor to reveal a lottery ticket and take a photo with the design that appears.
The last frontier...
hololive 5th fes.で歌われた名曲『The Last Frontier』からなんと！フィギュア化決定！
The masterpiece 'The Last Frontier' performed at hololive 5th fes. is finally getting a figure release!
スケールフィギュア化決定！星街すいせい / AZKi
Scale figures announced! Hoshimachi Suisei / AZKi
フリューから『ホロライブ』プライズが全国アミューズメント施設にて続々展開中！
Hololive prizes from FuRyu are rolling out at amusement centers nationwide!
パペットぬいぐるみ、寝そべりぬいぐるみ、指パペット、キャンディ缶。
Puppet plushes, Nesoberi plushes, finger puppets, and candy tins.
4月からは新たに、ひっかけフィギュアも登場！
Starting in April, new 'Hikkake' figures will also be available!
フリュー！
FuRyu!
台湾旅行中、最も便利な決済サービスを提供します。
Providing the most convenient payment service for your trip to Taiwan.
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony 一カ通限定盲包
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony iPASS Limited Blind Packs
歌いたい曲が入っていなかった...
The song I wanted to sing wasn't there...
だったらJOYSOUND X1で歌おうぜ！
Then let's sing with JOYSOUND X1!
JOYSOUND X1 俺の番！ JOYSOUND X1!
JOYSOUND X1, it's my turn! JOYSOUND X1!
JOYSOUND X1 曲数ナンバー1！
JOYSOUND X1, number one in song count!
AIが採点 絶賛 カラオケ最高 歌えるって最高！
AI scoring, highly acclaimed, karaoke is the best, singing is the best!
JOYSOUND REVOLUTION 見ようぜ 曲数No.1 歌いたい曲があるって最高
Check out JOYSOUND REVOLUTION! Number one in song count, it's great to have songs you want to sing
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: Information for Visitors
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援 OK です
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance / Cheering loudly is OK
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony PENLIGHT COLORS
#hololivefesEXPO25_DAY1
Color Rise Harmony
hololive 6th fes.
バンダイ、バンダイスピリッツより、
From Bandai and Bandai Spirits,
ホロライブデフォルメコレクション Vol.2
hololive Deformed Collection Vol.2
ホロライブエキスポ2025の会場にある特設ブースで
at the special booth in the Hololive Expo 2025 venue,
ガシャポン
Gashapon
Carddass
展示中の商品をご紹介。
introducing products on display.
LIFESTYLE BANDAI
ホロライブエキスポ2025限定の
Exclusive to hololive EXPO 2025,
一番くじ特設フォトブースも展開中。
a special Ichiban Kuji photo booth is also available.
モニターをタッチしてくじ券をめくり、
Touch the monitor to flip the ticket,
出てきたデザインと一緒に撮影できます。
and take a photo with the design that appears.
グッスマ！
Good Smile!
The Last Frontier...
...捧げる歌を...
...the song we dedicate...
...もう一度...
...once more...
...響きだす歌を...
...the song that begins to resonate...
フリューから「ホロライブ」プライズが
Hololive prizes from FuRyu are
全国アミューズメント施設にて続々展開中！
appearing in amusement facilities nationwide!
4月からは新たにひっかけフィギュアも登場！
Starting in April, new 'Hikkake Figures' will also be available!
フリュー
FuRyu
iPASS
歌いたい曲が入っていなかった
The song I wanted to sing wasn't there...
だったらJOYSOUND X1で歌おうぜ！
In that case, let's sing it on JOYSOUND X1!
JOYSOUND X1 ONLY ONE
JOYSOUND X1 曲数No.1
JOYSOUND X1, number one in song count
AIが採点 絶賛 カラオケ最高
AI scoring, acclaimed, karaoke is the best
歌いたい曲があるって最高
It's the best to have the songs you want to sing
JOYSOUND X1
タイトー
Taito
超特大ぬいぐるみブランド
From the super extra-large plushie brand
「どきゅーと」から商品化決定！
'Doqute,' commercialization is decided!
グルーヴコースター最新作に、
In the latest Groove Coaster game,
白上フブキと...
Shirakami Fubuki and...
さくらみこが、キャラクターボイスで参戦！
Sakura Miko are joining as character voices!
人気曲や、私たちが歌う曲も楽しめる！
Enjoy popular songs and the ones we sing!
私たちが、グルーヴワールドをナビゲートするよ！
We will navigate you through the Groove World!
コナミ
Konami
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony
開演までいましばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援 OK です
Cheering loudly is OK.
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
PENLIGHT COLORS
Color Rise Harmony Fan Messages
繋がる未来へ
To the connecting future
描いた景色が
The scenery we painted
今ここにあるから
Is right here right now
走り出した夢の鼓動
The heartbeat of the dream that started running
止まらないよ
It won't stop
響け
Resonate
色鮮やかに
In vivid colors
輝く世界
The shining world
手を伸ばした先に
At the end of our reaching hands
奇跡が待ってるから
Because a miracle is waiting
届け
Reach out
最高のステージ
The best stage
一緒に作ろう
Let's create it together
終わらない物語
A never-ending story
刻み込んで
Carving it in
奏でよう
Let's perform
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
To all visitors
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Due to performance reasons, please be aware of flashing lights
声出し応援 OK です
Cheering loudly is OK
Attention
For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK!!
PENLIGHT COLORS
Color Rise Harmony
hololive 6th fes.
I am supporting hololive 6th fes!
姫森ルーナ
Himemori Luna
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
星街すいせい
Hoshimachi Suisei
赤井はあと
Akai Haato
夏色まつり
Natsuiro Matsuri
不知火フレア
Shiranui Flare
白銀ノエル
Shirogane Noel
角巻わため
Tsunomaki Watame
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
姫森ルーナ
Himemori Luna
桃鈴ねね
Momosuzu Nene
ラプラス・ダークネス
La+ Darknesss
博衣こより
Hakui Koyori
ムーナ・ホシノヴァ
Moona Hoshinova
クレイジー・オリー
Kureiji Ollie
カエラ・コヴァルスキア
Kaela Kovalskia
IRyS
シオリ・ノヴェラ
Shiori Novella
古石ビジュー
Koseki Bijou
ネリッサ・レイヴンクロフト
Nerissa Ravencroft
フワワ・アビスガード
Fuwawa Abyssgard
モココ・アビスガード
Mococo Abyssgard
hololive 6th fes.
Color Rise Harmony
だって僕は星だから
Because I am a star
Stellar Stellar
きっと君はもう気付いていた
Surely you've already noticed
この心の奥で抱いた
The feelings I've held deep in my heart
それがこれから話すチープなモノローグさ
That's the cheap monologue I'm about to tell
ずっと言えない言葉があった
There were words I could never say
越せない壁があった
There was a wall I couldn't cross
ずっとさ
All this time
ずっとあの残り香とその匂いが
That lingering scent and its fragrance
どうしようもなく憎らしくて
I hated them so much I couldn't help it
部屋の隅で膝を抱えて
Hugging my knees in the corner of my room
震えていた
I was trembling
太陽なんていらないから
I don't need the sun or anything like it
上げないでいて
So please don't let it rise
その手を伸ばして
Reach out your hand
誰かに届くように
So that it reaches someone
僕だって君と同じ
Because even I, just like you
特別な誰かじゃないから
Am not someone special
そうさ夜を抱き寄せて
That's right, embrace the night
ありったけの輝きで
With all the radiance I have
この音がずっとずっと止まない
May this sound never, ever end
そうさずっと泣きたかったのは
That's right, the reason I wanted to cry all along
僕一人じゃないから
Was because I wasn't the only one
迎えに行こう王子様
Let's go meet them, Prince Charming
まだ...
Still...
だって僕は星だから
Because I am a star
なんてありふれた話なんだ
What a common story it is
理想だけ書き連ねていた
Just listing out ideals
ノートの隅に眠るホントのワンシーンだ
It's a true scene sleeping in the corner of a notebook
何回だって歌うんだ
I'll sing it as many times as it takes
明日なんて　来ないままでいて
Let tomorrow never come
その手を伸ばして
Reach out your hand
誰かに届くように
So it reaches someone
本当に大切なもののために
For the things that are truly important
お願いみたいなんだ
It's like a prayer
そうさ僕は夜を待って
That's right, I wait for the night
Stellar Stellar
ありのまま考えないで
Don't think, just be as you are
心音がきっときっと　止まらない
My heartbeat surely, surely won't stop
そうさ僕はずっと泣きたかったのは
That's right, the reason I've wanted to cry all this time
ありきたりな事じゃないさ
Isn't something ordinary
作りすぎた歌
A song made too much
夢に見るような
Like a fairy tale you'd see in a dream
おとぎ話らしい
Like a fairy tale
そうさ僕は夜を待って
That's right, I wait for the night
Stellar Stellar
ありたけの輝いて
Shine with all you've got
心音がずっとずっと　止まらない
My heartbeat forever and ever won't stop
そうさ僕は愛を待って
That's right, I wait for love
Stellar Stellar
世界中の真ん中で
In the middle of the whole world
心音がきっときっと　止まらない
My heartbeat surely, surely won't stop
そうさ僕はずっと泣きたかったのは
That's right, the reason I've wanted to cry all this time
待っていたシンデレラじゃないさ
Isn't the Cinderella I was waiting for
迎えにいこう王子様だ
Let's go meet them, I'm the prince
だって僕は星だから
Because I am a star
だって僕は星だった
Because I was a star
Stellar Stellar
6thフェス、始まります！
The 6th fes is starting!
みんな行くよー！
Everyone, let's go!
あの涙が
Those tears
今の僕らを繋いで
Connect us now
この心に
In this heart
君の欠片がいるから
Because pieces of you are here
一人じゃないから
Because I'm not alone
いつか描いた
Inside the words
文字の中
I once drew
目を閉じた先に
Beyond closed eyes
色付く景色が揺れた
The colorful scenery swayed
優しく戸惑う
Inside the gentle
風の中
Confusing wind
重なる花びら
Overlapping petals
僕たちの声
Our voices
一瞬
Every
Single moment
捕まえるみたいに
Like catching them
もっと
More
And more
踏み出せたなら
If only I could have stepped forward
あの涙が
Those tears
今の僕らを繋いで
Connect us now
この心に
In this heart
君の欠片がいるから
Because pieces of you are here
強くなくてもいい
It's okay not to be strong
今の光を
The light of right now...
ギュっと
Tighten it
集め
Gather it
空に放つ
And release it to the sky
この奇跡を
This miracle
僕らでそっと輝かせるから
Because we will make it shine softly
力が湧くから
Because strength wells up
あの手を
Those hands
握りしめて
Clutch them tight
遠い未来へと
To the distant future
強く願い込め巻いた
Wrapping it with a strong wish
希望の風を吹かせては
Letting the wind of hope blow
理想の花びら 祈る明日の空
Petals of ideals, praying to tomorrow's sky
何百億も光る星みたいに
Like hundreds of billions of shining stars
ずっとずっと終わらないから
Because it will never, ever end
この笑顔が一番強く抱きしめて
Embrace this smile the most strongly
今未来にこの手伸ばしてゆくから
Now I'll reach my hand out to the future
時に転んでも空を見上げよう
Even if we fall sometimes, let's look up at the sky
笑い日々を刻んでゆく
Carving our laughing days
次の夢を掴み取るって
That I'll grasp the next dream
約束するから
Because I promise
踏み出そうここから
Let's step forward from here
We are,
With you
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to see the same future
あの夢手にしたい
I want to make that dream mine
We are, with you.
Catch the moment.
降り注いだ奇跡の中へ
Into the miracle that poured down
その先まで続く空に紛れたら
If we get lost in the sky that continues beyond that
君の場所と今を繋げたくて
I want to connect your place and the present
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us now
この心に君のカケラがいるから
Because there's a piece of you in this heart
強くなくてもいい今の光を
It's okay not to be strong, take this light now
もっと集め空に放つ
Gather it more and release it into the sky
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせるから
Because we'll make this miracle shine gently
咲かせようここから
Let's make it bloom from here
一人じゃないから
Because you're not alone
へひっ！ ふふっ！
Hehi! Fufu!
幕張メッセの、みんなの脳髄に、アッシュッシュしちゃうぞー！
I'm going to inject all of your brains here at Makuhari Messe!
実験だ！実験だ！ジュケジュケ実験だ！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment! A juke-juke experiment!
実験だ！実験だ！うわーっ！実験だ！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment! Waaah! It's an experiment!
テケテケテケ！対決 解決 叙情中！
Teke-teke-teke! Confrontation, resolution, lyrical status!
酔っ払って飛び出てパピプペポ！
Getting drunk and popping out, pa-pi-pu-pe-po!
ケショケショケショ！化粧 アテンション プリーズ！
Kesho-kesho-kesho! Makeup, attention please!
ダメダメだっ！自棄糞しちゃうよ！
It's no good! I'm going to get desperate!
マヨって ダメダメ マヨって サイレンス
Mayo-ing is no good, Mayo-ing silence
マヨって 呪文は マヨマヨジュシュシュ！
The Mayo-ing spell is Mayo-Mayo-ju-shu-shu!
コヨ火のデザート 恋するハッピー
Koyo-fire dessert, falling in love happy
コヨ火に 焼かれて 恋い焦がれ！
Burned by the Koyo-fire, pining for love!
サイン コサイン タンジェント！ 事件勃発 ダイレクト！
Sine, Cosine, Tangent! Direct outbreak of an incident!
ハクいイノセンス！ 全身全霊 ダーリン！
White innocence! With all my soul, darling!
天才！ 天才！ 天才！ とんでもなくエナイ！
Genius! Genius! Genius! Unbelievably enough!
羽目を外して 褒めてください！
Let loose and please praise me!
最高！ 最高！ 最高！ 飛んでるって よっしゃ！
Best! Best! Best! It's flying, alright!
打ちのめすわ 三三七拍子！
I'll knock you out with a 3-3-7 beat!
感覚は爆発さ！ パチピポポ！
My senses are exploding! Pachi-pipo-po!
間違えて ドカン！ 予定通りよ この計算通り！
Mistake it and bang! It's just as planned, just as calculated!
実験だ！実験だ！ジュケジュケ実験だ！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment! A juke-juke experiment!
実験だ！実験だ！うわーっ！実験だ！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment! Waaah! It's an experiment!
実験だ！実験だ！ジュケジュケ実験だ！ 実験だ！実験だ！実験だー！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment! Juke-juke experiment! Experiment! Experiment! It's an experiment!
さーて、早速始めましょう！
Now then, let's get started right away!
これより行う、天才マッドサイエンティバレー！
From here on, the genius mad scienti-valley!
世にも奇妙なスンバラスィ大実験！
A very strange and wonderful big experiment!
良コンソメは雲のラボだと飛び
Good consommé flies as a cloud lab
ドキドキワクワク胸打つリズム
A heart-pounding and exciting rhythm
...計算通りよ
...Just as planned.
真剣なのをぶっ刺せば完了
Stick in a serious one and it's done.
ドクドク 打つ
Thump, thump, it beats
波動
Waveform
原子番号315番 こよりにうむ
Atomic number 315, Koyorynium.
これは 幸せになる 最高のニュースだよ
This is the best news to make you happy!
病みつきになっちゃえばいいじゃん！
It's okay to get addicted!
欲しいなら 叫べばいいじゃん！
If you want it, just scream!
大好きですかー？
Do you love me?
幸せですかー？
Are you happy?
愛すれば 救われる
If you love, you'll be saved.
あぁ なんて素敵な 世界なんでしょう
Ah, what a wonderful world it is.
一途なその瞳で
With those devoted eyes,
見つめて 推して 燃えて 解けちゃえ
Stare, support, burn, and melt away!
明るい未来に 乾杯！
Cheers to a bright future!
天才 天才 天才
Genius, genius, genius
ハチャメチャに スカイ
Messily high up in the sky
ハツラツで オッケー
Vibrantly okay
コズミックスタイル
Cosmic Style
最高 最高 最高
The best, the best, the best
今日も 爆熱っ子
A super hot kid today too
本気度 ウルトラ
Sincerity level: Ultra
サンデイ ラボレーション
Sunday Laboration
人生は
Life is...
爆発だ！
An explosion!
ポジトビポッパッパ
Positovipoppappa
やっぱり 万事 解決
As expected, everything's solved
どこまでも
To the very end,
計算通り
just as planned
Just as planned
計算通りよ
実験だ！ 実験だ！
An experiment! An experiment!
実験だ！
An experiment!
少年少女 舞え 舞え 負け
Boys and girls, dance, dance, lose
ホロライブ 6th fes.!
hololive 6th fes.!
I want to hear you scream!
みんな もっと 一緒に 飛ぼうか！
Everyone, let's jump more together!
かかってこいよー！
Bring it on!
Are you ready?
白いアホウを耳に当て 少しニヤッとして挨拶する
Putting white nonsense to my ear, I grin a little and greet.
染み込んだ この青田が 弱音を吐いた 瞬間を 溢れ出す
This soaked green field overflows the moment it voices complaints.
意味の無いまま 見えない目を 凝らしたの 望む空で
Meaninglessly, I strained my unseeing eyes in the desired sky.
あの日 誘致した 距離から 未だ 取り戻せた 鼓動が 鳴り響きそう
From the distance lured that day, the heartbeat I regained still seems ready to echo.
見失って 辛くて 世界を
Losing sight, suffering, the world...
嫌った 人の
of the person who hated it
ひどく不順な個性 固定してちゃ 未来は生み出せない
With such impure individuality fixed, a future can't be born.
少年少女 前を向け 暮れる 演全さ 束の間 だって
Boys and girls, look forward, even if the dazzling twilight is but a moment.
連れ戻せ 連れ戻せ 三日月が 赤く 燃え上がる さぁさ
Bring it back, bring it back, the crescent moon burns red, come on.
衝動 ゼロで 刻め 掃攘 楽勝 尖らせ 界へ
Carve it with zero impulse, sweeping away with ease, sharpening toward the world.
オーバー 妄想 戦線 Hey!
Over-delusion battlefront, Hey!
お先にどうぞって 芝居打つ 次の 舞台 無茶苦茶に 決める
Acting as if saying "after you", I messily decide the next stage.
ほら 出番だ パスワードで 目を覚ました ジャンジャジャーン 今は
Look, it's showtime, waking up with a password, ta-da! Now,
止まらない もう 夜が 深くなる お子様なら 燃える 延長戦
it won't stop, the night is deepening, for the kids, it's a burning overtime.
逆境 具合 クールだろ めげないで まだまだ ほら 早く 早く
The adversity is cool, right? Don't give up, come on, faster, faster.
インテンポで 視線 合わせて ハイタッチ ビートが 鳴り出せば
High-fiving in tempo while locking eyes, once the beat starts,
考えてちゃ 遅いって ほら 乗っかって こうぜ ゼイ！
it's too late to think, come on, let's ride it, Zei!
ワンコードで 視線 合わせて ぶっ飛んだ グルーヴが 渦巻けば
Locking eyes on a single chord, once the crazy groove swirls,
御乱心じゃない 見えるはず その ハイエンドルフィン 決まりさ
It's not madness, you should see it, that high endorphin is for sure.
ド派手な 暑さも 擦り違う 空手 価値観も
Even the flashy heat and the karate-like values that pass each other by,
悪くないだろ 目を見開いて 手を取り合ったら
aren't bad, right? If we open our eyes and take each other's hands,
案外 チープな ことだも 合言葉 なんて 言える
it's surprisingly cheap stuff, we can even say things like passwords.
少しだけ 前を 向ける
We can look forward just a little.
少年少女 前を向け 暮れる 縁絶する 希望を だって
Boys and girls, look forward, for even the hope that speechifies twilight...
思い出して 口に出す 公式なんて 合図 お別れを
...recall it and speak it out, formulas and signals, a farewell.
ねぇ 無垢な 世界のこと 散々 だって 笑い飛ばせたんだ
Hey, about the innocent world, we could laugh it off no matter how bad it was.
合図 終わりる
The signal ends.
少年少女 前を向け 暮れる 演全さ 束の間 だって
Boys and girls, look forward, even if the dazzling twilight is but a moment.
掴み取れ 掴み取れ 太陽が 赤く 燃え上がる さぁさ
Seize it, seize it, the sun burns red, come on.
コード 最強に しようさ 全力 その目を 見開いた
Let's make the chord the strongest, with full power, you opened those eyes.
オーバー 妄想 戦線 感情性の 迷路の 先へ
Over-delusion battlefront, beyond the maze of emotionality.
Thank you!
夏色まつり
Natsuiro Matsuri
桃鈴ねね
Momosuzu Nene
ラプラス・ダークネス
La+ Darknesss
Ready Go!
さとるコールで叫び勝ち
Winning with an enlightened call!
ほとんど同じポーズ取りがち
We tend to strike the same poses!
Yeah! 皆 指差し確認
Yeah! Everyone, point and check!
マルチエキサイティング！
Multi-exciting!
Can't stop it! 考えてみな
Can't stop it! Just think about it,
皆 大人しくコールするんだぞ いけるか？
everyone, call out politely! Are you ready?
うりゃおい！うりゃおい！
Urya oi! Urya oi!
ジャージャー！
Jya-jya-!
あー！ねねちゃん！
Ah! Nene-chan!
あー！ラプちゃん！
Ah! Lapu-chan!
俺の！まつりちゃん！
My! Matsuri-chan!
あー！ラプちゃん！
Ah! Lapu-chan!
あー！まつりちゃん！
Ah! Matsuri-chan!
ねねちゃん！ねねちゃん！
Nene-chan! Nene-chan!
オーイング！
Oing!
オーイング！オーイング！オーイング！
Oing! Oing! Oing!
意味なんて考えるほうが負け
If you think about the meaning, you lose!
次々と止まらない
It doesn't stop, one after another!
サビで振り込む
Sending it in at the chorus!
急に静かになり 黙々と踊るヲタク
Suddenly getting quiet, the otakus dance silently!
ひと段落したら 叫ぶおい！うりゃ！おい！
Once it settles, scream: Oi! Urya! Oi!
せーの、さあ跳べ 燃えるアカメ
One, two, jump! Burning red eyes!
シキメシタベル お酒は20歳になってからでーす
Eat the ceremonial meal! You have to be 20 to drink alcohol!
これこそが生きがい しまいにゃ歌い出す Oh Yeah
This is what I live for! We'll end up singing along, Oh Yeah!
フラフラ僕らと君の愛 それララララバイ
Dizzy, our and your love, that's a la-la-lullaby!
うりゃおい！
Urya oi!
虎！
Tiger!
火！
Fire!
継続！
Continuity!
あー！ねねちゃん！
Ah! Nene-chan!
初見殺しの頂点 ガンガンついていく 超共鳴のフロア
The peak of punishing first-timers! Following along fiercely in this hyper-resonant floor!
パンパン！ポケモンパン！
Pan-pan! Pokemon Pan!
フレッシュブレッド伊東パン！
Fresh Bread, Ito Pan!
松たか子！
Matsu Takako!
ヤマザキ春のパンまつり！
Yamazaki Spring Bread Festival!
三拍手して 合図入れたくなっちゃう そう思ったらすぐに戻るんだって
Clap three times, wanting to give the signal. If you feel that way, you'll be back in an instant!
なゆれと止まらない
Swaying, it doesn't stop!
もっと振り込む
Sending it in even more!
やっとサビになるぞと 黙々と踊るヲタク
Knowing the chorus is finally here, the otakus dance silently!
もう覚えたでしょ 叫ぶおい！うりゃ！おい！
You've learned it by now, right? Scream: Oi! Urya! Oi!
せーの、さあ跳べ
One, two, jump!
間近に目 勝ち得チケット
Eyes up close, a winning ticket!
弾む定番に命かけてんです
Risking my life for this classic beat!
推ししか見えない 結局言いたいヤツ Oh Yeah
I can only see my fave! In the end, I'm just the guy who wants to say... Oh Yeah!
言いたいことがあるんだ！
There's something I want to say!
何何！
What, what!
やっぱりかわいいよ！
You're just so cute after all!
何何！
What, what!
やっと見つけたお姫様
The princess I finally found!
何何！
What, what!
俺が生まれてきた理由
The reason I was born!
何何！
What, what!
それはお前に出会うため
It was to meet you!
何何！
What, what!
俺と一緒に人生歩もう
Let's walk through life together!
何何！
What, what!
世界で一番愛してる
I love you most in the world!
何何！
What, what!
ア・イ・シ・テ・ル！
I. LOVE. YOU!
ワールドカオス！
World Chaos!
諸星！
Moroboshi!
時雨！
Shigure!
神楽！
Kagura!
金剛山！
Kongousan!
翔襲叉！
Shoushuusa!
黒！
Black!
なぎ倒せ 遺伝子レベルで刻み込まれてるヲタク もう我慢できない うずうずしょうがない
Mow them down! Otakus with it carved in their DNA! I can't take it anymore, I'm itching to go!
サビで振り込む
Sending it in at the chorus!
急に静かになり 黙々と踊るヲタク
Suddenly getting quiet, the otakus dance silently!
ひと段落したら 叫ぶおい！うりゃ！おい！
Once it settles, scream: Oi! Urya! Oi!
せーの、さあ跳べ 燃えるアカメ
One, two, jump! Burning red eyes!
シキメシタベル お酒は20歳になってからでーす
Eat the ceremonial meal! You have to be 20 to drink alcohol!
これこそが生きがい しまいにゃ歌い出す Oh Yeah
This is what I live for! We'll end up singing along, Oh Yeah!
フラフラ僕らと君の愛 それララララバイ
Dizzy, our and your love, that's a la-la-lullaby!
ワクワク止まらないんだ 無敵のラララバイ Oh Yeah!
The excitement doesn't stop, the invincible la-la-lullaby, Oh Yeah!
うりゃおい！
Urya oi!
虎！
Tiger!
火！
Fire!
人造！
Artificial!
繊維！
Fiber!
海女！
Diver!
振動！
Vibration!
化繊！
Synthetic!
飛・除去！
Fly-Removal!
うわーーー！ありがとうーーー！
Whoa! Thank you!
皆、見てくれてありがとう！
Thank you all for watching!
皆、来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you all for coming!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
おつにおーーみんな！
Thanks for tuning in, everyone!
すごかったねー！
That was amazing, wasn't it!
すごかったよ！
It was amazing!
吾輩の方がすごいけどね。
I'm even more amazing, though.
パン、パン、パン、パン！ポケモンパン！フレッシュ！フレッシュ！
Clap, clap, clap, clap! Pokemon Pan! Fresh! Fresh!
なんでヲタクに言わせない！？
Why didn't you let the otaku say it!?
吾輩から言う……似合ってるから！
I'll say it... because it looks good on you!
もう、ねね疲れちゃった……。
Geez, Nene's already tired...
頑張ったからね。頑張った、頑張った。
Because you worked hard. You did it, you did it.
吾輩が一番好きなのこれ。
This is my favorite one.
あ、ちょっと自己紹介しよ！自己紹介。そうだね。
Ah, let's do self-introductions! Right.
じゃあ、先輩から！
Then, starting from our senior!
はい！じゃあ、みんなオレンジ色見せてくれるかな？
Okay! Everyone, can you show me some orange?
すごいな。めっちゃあっちまでオレンジ！
Amazing. It's orange all the way over there!
はい、みんな！ホロライブの清楚担当、みんなのアイドル、夏色まつりです！
Hello everyone! Hololive's 'purity' representative, everyone's idol, Natsuiro Matsuri here!
ちょっとまつりやりたいことあるんです、ついでにやっていいですか？
There's something Matsuri wants to do, can I do it while I'm at it?
今からまつりが「夏色まつりは清楚だよな？」って聞くんで、清楚だ！と思って反応してください。
I'm going to ask 'Natsuiro Matsuri is pure, right?' so please respond thinking 'She is pure!'
夏色まつりは清楚だよなー！
Natsuiro Matsuri is pure, right?!
おい！聞こえてない。聞こえてない質問もあるか……。
Hey! I can't hear you. Maybe there are some questions I didn't hear...
次、ねねち、ねねち！
Next, Nenechi, Nenechi!
あの、茶を濁してください。
Um, please change the subject.
みんなそのままオレンジで大丈夫い！イェーイ！
Everyone, you can stay orange! Yay!
みんな、ねねが「みんなの心の」って言ったら「エナジードリンク」で返してね。
Everyone, when Nene says 'Your heart's', please respond with 'Energy Drink'.
ホロライブ五期生、ねぽらぼの、みんなの心の……
Hololive 5th Generation, of NePoLaBo, your heart's...
エナジードリンク！
Energy Drink!
桃鈴ねねです！今日よろしく！
I'm Momosuzu Nene! Let's have fun today!
本当に同じ観客ですかさっきと？
Is this really the same audience as before?
うん、同じだよね、みんな。
Yeah, they're the same, right everyone?
全然声量が……
The volume is totally...
ねねに優しい！まんまん！
They're kind to Nene! Perfect!
ほら、じゃあオレンジじゃないやつ行けよ。
Look, go for something not orange then.
じゃあいつもの、いいですか？
Then, the usual, are you ready?
貴様ら！跪け！
You lot! Kneel!
Yes, My Dark!
吾輩のお名前は、ラプラス・ダークネスだ！
My name is La+ Darknesss!
すいちゃんから始まって、我々も来ましたけど。
Starting with Sui-chan, we've arrived as well.
ちなみに二人は何歌うんですか？ねねち何歌うの？
By the way, what are you two singing? Nenechi, what are you singing?
ねねは新しい曲を歌うんだけど……あ、X（Twitter）でポストしたから、
Nene is going to sing a new song... ah, I posted about it on X,
みんなさすがに覚えてきてくれたよね？
so everyone remembered it and came, right?
覚えてなかったら処刑だからな。
If you didn't remember, it's execution.
だってもね、あ、もうコール完璧だと思うんで。
Because, well, I think the calls will be perfect.
みんな完璧だよね？完璧だよね？
Everyone's perfect, right? Right?
ほら！最前列の海外ニキがさ、ほら「イェーイ！」って言ってくれてる。
Look! The overseas fans in the front row, see, they're saying 'Yay!'
めっちゃ分かりやすい。ねっ子めっちゃ分かりやすい。
It's so clear. The Nekko (Husbandos) are so easy to spot.
ねっ子発見！ねっ子発見！抜いてこ、抜いてこ。
Nekko found! Nekko found! Let's pull them out.
まつり先輩はどうなんですか？
How about you, Matsuri-senpai?
まつりはね……内緒！
As for Matsuri... it's a secret!
でもオリジナル曲で、今までにはない感じの曲。
But it's an original song, and it has a vibe I haven't done before.
今日、女まつりすの子も来ていると思うんですけど。
I think there are female Matsurisu (fans) here today as well.
その子がちょっと共感できるような感じかな？
I think it's a song they might be able to relate to.
皆さん、なんと吾輩……
Everyone, amazingly, I...
この後歌います！
...will be singing right after this!
知らなかった！リハも見せてくれないし。
I didn't know! You wouldn't even let us see the rehearsal.
じゃ次は我が輩歌うんですけども、盛り上げてほしいね。
Well, I'll be singing next, so I want you all to get fired up.
みんな盛り上げてほしい！
I want everyone to get fired up!
いっぱい！もっと！
A lot! More!
声出せますかー！？
Can I hear your voices!?
ありがとね。
Thank you.
そして、はい、えーとですね、残念ですが...
And, yes, well, unfortunately...
ここで！
at this point!
無料パートが終わり！
The free part ends!
おーーわり！
It's ovーーer!
ま、でもね、あの、ま、みんなラプラスの歌聴きたいと思うから...
Well, but you see, I think everyone wants to hear La+'s singing...
当たり前だろお前ら！
Of course they do, you guys!
みんなね、是非楽しんでくれればと思います。
So I hope everyone will enjoy it.
そしてですね、え、ハッシュタグ「#ホロライブフェスエキスポ25_DAY1」で、
And also, with the hashtag "#hololivefesEXPO25_DAY1,"
ツイ、ポストお願いします！
please tweet and post!
ツイ、ポ、ポストね。お願いします。
Twee, po, post, right. Please do.
はい、というわけで、本当に本当に無料パートはここまでになります。
Alright, so the free part really, truly ends here.
概要欄からチケットのご購入をよろしくお願いします！
Please purchase tickets from the description field!
お願いしまーす！
Please!
もちろん我が輩だけでなく、
Of course, not just me,
この後もめちゃめちゃめちゃめちゃ...この二人も含めてね！
but after this, so many, many... including these two!
はい！そうだよ！
Yes! That's right!
ホロメンがみんな頑張って歌って踊るので、よろしくね！
All the Holomem will be working hard singing and dancing, so look forward to it!
よろしくねー！
Look forward to it!
我々最初のMCパートということでね、今後ちょっと恒例になる合図っていうのをみんなにもやってもらおうかなと思ってて。
Since this is our first MC part, I thought I'd have everyone do a sign that will become a regular thing from now on.
じゃ、まつりさんが「せーの！」って言ったら、みんなで「Color Rise Harmony!」って言ってください。
So, when I say "Ready, go!", everyone please say "Color Rise Harmony!"
オッケー！
Okay!
行くよー！
Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, go!
Color Rise Harmony!
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended! Thank you for watching!
This sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching.